The Seven Shadows want their operation to succeed!
I see everyone is here.
Yes, Lady Alpha.
The Seven Shadows are all here.
It sure is rare having all Seven Shadows together.
It’s because a certain someone is always missing.
Zeta is part of the intelligence unit,
so it can’t be helped.
That’s how it is, puppy.
Eh? Did you just say something?
Oh, nothing…
Ugh, so sleepy…
Ah, Delta is not sleepy!
I didn’t hear anyone mention a puppy.
Grrrrrr!
Isn’t it about time we get down to business?
So, what’s the situation?
Right, thanks to the
Demonic Possession Search Device…
Developed by Eta that
commenced operation last month…
Shadow Garden finally has
over six hundred members.
Six hundred?!
That’s a lot of people.
Eta developed it based on
the teachings of Lord Shadow.
V, V, V…
Still, that’s an incredible number of people.
Great job, Eta.
However…
It’s still not enough, right?
Right.
To create the world Shadow has envisioned…
We must gather more and more allies.
That’s why today’s operation must be perfect.
You could say that.
Now then, we will begin the operation at once.
Beta, report to Shadow.
Yes, ma’am.
Move all teams to their assigned positions.
Yes, ma’am!
What’s wrong?
Actually, I just have one question.
What is it?
How much is six hundred?
Haha!
It’s full to bursting.
I got it!
It’s full to bursting!